Guide to the Laura Foreman Papers 1949-2001 MSS.122
Fales Library and Special Collections
Laura Foreman Papers
1949-2001
1967-2001
Fales Library and Special Collections
Foreman, Laura
MSS.122
133.74 Linear Feet (122 records cartons, 27 photo binders, 2 document cases and 5 oversize boxes)
Laura Foreman was a dancer, choreographer, visual artist, writer and director of dance at New School University. She lived and worked in New York City from the mid-1960s until her death. Material in the Laura Foreman Papers related to Foreman's art includes project notes, sketches and drafts, photographic and audiovisual documentation, grant applications, props, art objects, and press clippings. Material related to Foreman's personal life includes correspondence, personal notes, journals, and appointment books. The collection also contains course planning materials and administrative files related to Foreman's career at the New School.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Laura Foreman was a dancer, choreographer, visual artist, writer and director of dance at New School University. She lived and worked in New York City from the mid-1960s until her death.
Foreman worked primarily in dance for the first decade of her time in Manhattan, operating both the Laura Foreman Dance Company and Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre with her husband, John Watts. In the late 1970s she began working in more abstract performance and visual art. Perhaps her most well-known piece was 1981's "Wallwork," a collaboration with Watts which took the form of a rigorous advertising campaign for a nonexistent performance.
After Watts's death in 1982, Foreman's work shifted towards visual art and writing. She created an extensive sculpture series, "Birdhouse as Metaphor," which consisted of numerous functional and non-functional birdhouses and showed in 1990 at Souyun Yi Gallery. In 1997, Close Encounters, a volume of Foreman's short stories, was published by Outloud Books.
Foreman died of cancer in Manhattan in 2001.
Source:
Dunning, Jennifer. "Laura Foreman, 64, Director Of Dance at the New School." The New York Times, July 5, 2001.
Stage Works:
- Solo Suite (1967)
- A Time (1968)
- Perimeters (1969)
- Untitled (1970)
- Epicycles (1970)
- Signals (1970)
- glass and shadows (1971)
- Laura's Dance (1971)
- Songandance (1972)
- Margins (1972)
- Spaces (1972)
- Locrian (1973)
- Performance (1973)
- city of angels (1974)
- a deux (1974)
- Postludes (1974)
- Bud / Monopoly (1975)
- Program (1976)
- Heirlooms (1977)
- Entries (1978)
Artworks:
- TimeCoded Woman (1979-80)
- Coney Island Cray-Pas (1981)
- Philadelphia Story (1981)
- Poetry Peep Show (1981)
- Roomwork (1981)
- Wallwork (1981)
- Reclining Nudes (1982)
- Sweet Land of Liberty (1983)
- Word Painting / I have nothing to paint and I'm painting it (1983)
- Birdhouse as Metaphor (1989-93)
- Cry Uncle (1991)
- Window on the World (1995)
- Shacks of America (undated)
Written Works:
- A Message to Michael (1990)
- Close Encounters (1997)
Arrangement
Materials are arranged almost entirely as they were received. The collection was processed at the box level; a description of contents is given for each box. These descriptions are in no way comprehensive. See the Arrangement Notes for each series for more specific details. Loose items and those in need of special preservation attention were appropriately housed, and all efforts were made to preserve the collection's original arrangement.
Missing Title
Series I: Files
Series II: Notebooks, Address Books and Date Books
Series III: Correspondence
Series IV: Photographic Material
Series V: Artworks, Sketches and Posters
Series VI: Video recordings
Series VII: Films
Series VIII: Sound recordings
Series IX: Objects
Oversize Series I: Files
Oversize Series IV: Photographic Material
Oversize Series V: Artworks, Sketches and Posters
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated to the Fales Library by Laura Foreman in 1999.
Scope and Content
The Laura Foreman Papers contain materials pertaining to Foreman's life as a dancer, choreographer, visual and performance artist, as well as her personal life and career as Director of the Dance Department at the New School. Material related to Foreman's works includes project notes, sketches and drafts, photographic and audiovisual documentation, grant applications, props, art objects, and press clippings. Material related to Foreman's personal life includes correspondence, personal notes, journals, and appointment books. The collection also contains course planning materials and administrative files related to Foreman's career at the New School. Items in the collection date as far back as 1949, but the bulk of the collection covers a range from 1967 until Foreman's death in 2001.
The collection is divided into eight series:
SERIES I: Files contains documents and items related to Foreman's personal life and artistic career, including project drafts, personal notes, source material and press clippings.
SERIES II: Notebooks, Address Books and Date Books contains bound notebooks relating to Foreman's personal and artistic life, as well as originally collocated notecards.
SERIES III: Correspondence contains correspondence, primarily addressed to Foreman and dealing mostly with her personal life. A small portion of the correspondence pertains to her professional and artistic life.
SERIES IV: Photographic Material contains photographic prints, color slides, contact sheets and negatives pertaining both to Foreman's personal life and to her work as a choreographer and visual artist.
SERIES V: Artworks, Sketches and Posters contains primarily visual material produced by Foreman, including sketches, drafts, and posters from her own as well as others' performances and exhibitions.
SERIES VI: Video recordings contains Foreman's collection of video documentation of her dance performances and other artworks and exhibitions.
SERIES VII: Films contains a small amount of moving image documentation captured on film instead of video.
SERIES VIII: Sound recordings contains audio recordings.
SERIES IX: Objects contains various items once owned by Foreman or employed in her artworks, including props from dance performances.
OVERSIZE SERIES includes materials too large to be stored in a records carton or photo binder.
Series I: Files
Series IV: Photographic Material
Series V: Artworks, Sketches and Posters
Related Materials
John Watts Papers (MSS.093)
Robert Alexander Papers (MSS.114)
Separated Materials
The following materials have been removed to Fales Downtown Collection, Fales Special Collections and Fales American Collection:
Art now 74: a celebration of the American arts. Washington, D.C.: Artrend Foundation, 1974.
The comics journal. Vol. 111. Bethel, CT: Comics Journal, 1986.
Downtown. No. 40. New York, N.Y.: Arts Weekly, 1987.
Foreman, Laura. Close encounters: a book of short stories. Claryville, N.Y.: Outloud Books, 1997.
Fujimura, Makoto. Makoto Fujimura: works '90-'92. Tokyo: Tamaya Gallery, 1992.
Fujimura, Makoto, and International Arts Movement. Wouldest thou love.... New York, N.Y.: International Arts Movement, c1991.
Posters.; Art, Modern -- 20th century; Black-and-white negatives.; Notebooks; Color negatives.; Color slides.; Correspondence.; Sketchbooks.; Clippings (information artifacts); Address books.; Files.; Appointment books.; Painting (image-making); Negatives (photographic); Modern dance -- New York (State) -- New York; Contact sheets.; Modern dance|z United States.; Dance photography.; Schematic drawings.; Women artists -- United States.; Public art -- New York (State) -- New York.; Installations (Art) -- United States.; New York (N.Y.).; Performance artists.; Photographic prints.; Sculpture, American |z New York (State) |z New York |y 20th century.; Choreography -- United States; Notes.; Audiotapes.; Videocassettes.; Shimazaki, Satoru; Oleaga, Milton; Moore, Peter, 1932-1993; Alexander, Robert, 1947-; Watts, John, 1930-1982
- Series I: Files, 93.5 Linear Feet 75 Paige Cartons - 1 filed legal, 74 filed letter
  Scope and Content note
  Series I contains general files, mostly from Foreman's personal hanging file. The contents of this series relate to nearly all facets of Foreman's life and work.
  Arrangement note
  All efforts were made to preserve the original arrangement of the collection. Series I is described at the box level, with a listing of the types of files that are ostensibly contained within. These file types, generated by the finding aid author, are as follows:
  Administrative Materials
  Documentation
  Drafts
  Financial Files
  Grant Materials
  Outlines
  Personal Files
  Press
  Production Files
  Publishers' Files
  Source Material
  Teaching Materials
  Each file type is annotated parenthetically when it pertains to a specific medium or organization. Each box is then annotated, when applicable, with a list of specific works that are referenced within the materials in the box (see Biographical Note for list of works).
  - Drafts (Writing), Publishers' Files, Source Material, 1995-2001; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 1)
    General
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Close Encounters
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717720
  - Drafts and Outlines (Writing), Personal Files, Source Material, 1987-1998; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 2)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717738
  - Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 3)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717746
  - Personal Files, Source Material, 1990-1997; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 4)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717753
  - Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Source Material, 1991-1992; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 5)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717761
  - Outlines (Writing), Personal Files, Publishers' Files, Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 6)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717779
  - Documentation and Outlines (Art), Publishers' Files, Source Material, 1994; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 7)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717787
  - Documentation, Outlines (Writing), Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 8)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Coney Island Cray-Pas, Roomwork, Sweet Land of Liberty, Wallwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717795
  - Administrative Materials (Composer's and Choreographer's Theatre, Laura Foreman Dance Company), Outlines (Performance), Personal Files, Press, Production Files, Teaching Materials, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 9)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, TimeCoded Woman
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717803
  - Documentation, Grant Applications, Press, 1981-1993; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 10)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Coney Island Cray-Pas, Roomwork, Wallwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717811
  - Grant materials, Personal Files, 1994-2000; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 11)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717829
  - Administrative Materials (New School), Grant Materials, Personal Files, 1986-1995; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 12)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717837
  - Administrative Files (New School), 1995; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 13)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717845
  - Drafts (Writing), Grant Materials, 1985-1996; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 14)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717852
  - Administrative Materials, Grant Materials, 1990-1994; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 15)
    Works Referenced: Roomwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717860
  - Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 16)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717878
  - Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 17)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717886
  - Administrative Materials (Art, Writing), Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 18)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717894
  - Administrative Materials (Art, Writing), Documentation, Grant Materials, Press, 1985-2000; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 19)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Roomwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717902
  - Administrative Materials (Art, Composer's and Choreographer's Theatre), Personal Files, 1986-1999; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 20)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717910
  - Personal Files, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 21)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717928
  - Grant Materials, Personal Files, 1985-1997; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 22)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717936
  - Grant Materials, 1990-1999; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 23)
    continued from Box 22
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717944
  - Grant Materials, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 24)
    continued from Box 23
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717951
  - Grant Materials (cont'd from Box 24), Personal Files, Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 25)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717969
  - Personal Files, Source Material, Teaching Materials, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 26)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717977
  - Administrative Files (Art), Source Material, 1993; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 27)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Shacks of America
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717985
  - Administrative (Art), Press, Source Material, 1981-1993; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 28)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Wallwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050717993
  - Personal Files, Teaching Materials, 1976-1994; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 29)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718009
  - Personal Files, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 30)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718017
  - Administrative Materials and Financial Files (Composer's and Choreographer's Theatre), Personal Files, 1967-1988; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 31)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718025
  - Administrative Materials (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), Source Material, 1970-1985; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 32)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718033
  - Drafts (Writing), 1975-1985; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 33)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718041
  - Drafts (Writing), Source Material, 1985-1987; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 34)
    Works Referenced: TimeCoded Woman
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718058
  - Documentation, Drafts, Source Material, 1981; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 35)
    Works Referenced: Sweet Land of Liberty, TimeCoded Woman, Wallwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718066
  - Documentation, Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 36)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718074
  - Documentation, Outlines, Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 37)
    continued from box 36
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718082
  - Documentation, Outlines, Source Material, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 38)
    continued from box 37
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718090
  - Administrative Materials, Financial Files, Grant Materials, Source Material, Teaching Materials, 1966; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 39)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718108
  - Administrative Materials, Grant Applications, Press, 1968-1980; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 40)
    Offsite Barcode: 3114205071811
  - Administrative Materials (New School), Press, Source Material, 1987-1991; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 41)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718124
  - Drafts, Source Material, 1982-1986; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 42)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Shacks of America, A Message to Michael, TimeCoded Woman
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718132
  - Production Files (Laura Foreman Dance Company, Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), 1971-1977; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 43)
    Original box labeled "L.F. Dance Notes," in pencil
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718157
  - Personal Files, Source Material, 1981-1995; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 44)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718165
  - Personal Files, Production Files (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), Source Material, 1972-1999; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 45)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718173
  - Administrative Materials (Laura Foreman Dance Theatre, Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Press, Source Material, Teaching Materials, 1971-1996; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 46)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718181
  - Administrative Materials and Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Press, Source Material, 1974-1983; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 47)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718199
  - Administrative Materials (Writing), Personal Files, Publishers' Files, Source Material, 1990-1995; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 paige carton (Box 48)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718207
  - Admnistrative Materials (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre, Writing), Drafts (Writing), Grant Materials, Personal Files, Press, Publishers' Files, Source Material, Teaching Material, 1977-1997; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 paige carton (Box 49)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718215
  - Financial Files (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), 1988-1992; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 paige carton (Box 50)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718223
  - Personal Files, Source Material, Teaching Materials, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 paige carton (Box 51)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718231
  - Writing Source Material, Publishers' Files, Writing Drafts, Administrative Files (Laura Foreman Dance Company, Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 52)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718249
  - Administrative Materials (Art, Writing), Drafts (Writing), Source Material, 1987-1990; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 53)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718256
  - Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Publishers' Files, Source Material, Teaching Materials, 1991-1994; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 54)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718264
  - Administrative Materials (Art, Writing, New School), 1985-1996; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 55)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718272
  - Administrative Materials (New School), Teaching Materials, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 56)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718280
  - Personal Files, Teaching Materials, 1993; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 57)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718298
  - Administrative Materials (Art), Drafts (Writing), Grant Materials, Personal Files, Press, Source Material, Teaching Materials, 1990-1991; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 paige carton (Box 58)
    Works referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Reclining Nudes
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718306
  - Administrative Materials (Laura Foreman Dance Company, Writing), Drafts (Writing), Documentation (Performance), Press, 1977-1996; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 59)
    Works Referenced: Roomwork, Wallwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718314
  - Administrative Materials (Laura Foreman Dance Company), Grant Materials, Personal Files, Publishers' Files, Source Material, 1974-1996; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 60)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Shacks of America, Time Coded Woman
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718322
  - Drafts (Writing), Documentation, Financial Files (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), Personal Files, Press, Publishers' Files, Source Material, 1989-1990; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 61)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718330
  - Administrative Materials (New School), Grant Materials, Personal Files Source Material, 1995-1996; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 62)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718348
  - Administrative Files, Drafts (Writing), Grant Materials, Personal Files, Press, Teaching Materials, 1988-1990; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 63)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718363
  - Drafts (Writing), Financial Files (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), Grant Materials, Personal Files, Publishers' Files, Source Material, Teaching Materials, 1987-1989; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 64)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718371
  - Administrative Materials (Art, Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), Personal Files, Source Material, 1984-1992; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 65)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718389
  - Administrative Materials (Art), Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Press, Source Material, Teaching Materials, 1991-1993; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 66)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718397
  - Administrative Materials, Grant Materials, Personal Files, Press, Source Material, 1970-1987; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 67)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718405
  - Administrative Materials (Art), Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Publihser's Files, Source Material, 1982-1992; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 68)
    Works Referenced: A Message to Michael, Shacks of America, Time Coded Woman
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718413
  - Drafts (Writing), Personal Files, Source Material, 1982-1991; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 69)
    Works Referenced: A Message to Michael
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718421
  - Administrative Materials (Art), Personal Files, 1988-1999; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 70)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718439
  - Administrative Materials (Art), Personal Files, Press, 1960-1989; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 71)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, Reclining Nudes
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718447
  - Administrative Materials (Art), Personal Files, Writing Drafts, 1989-1990; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 72)
    Works Referenced: Birdhouse as Metaphor, TimeCoded Woman, Wallwork
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718454
  - Administrative Materials (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), Drafts (Art), Press, 1961-1994; 1 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (filed legal) (Box 73)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718462
  - Administrative Materials and Finanical Files (Composers' and Choreographers' Theatre), 1978-1990; 1 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 74)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718470
  - Administrative Materials (Performance), Documentation (Art), Personal Files, Press, 1971-2001; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 Paige Carton (Box 75)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718629
- Series II: Notebooks, Address Books and Date Books, 10 Linear Feet 8 paige cartons
  Series II contains notebooks, address books, date books and bundled notecards found loose during the processing of the collection. The contents range from performance notes, to daily planners, to personal memoranda.
  The contents of this series are arranged chronologically. A great deal of the notebooks and cards are undated; these are housed at the end of the series, grouped together as found.
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, 1963-1985 (Box 76)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718496
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, 1985-1994 (Box 77)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718504
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, 1994-1997 (Box 78)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718512
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, 1997-1998 (Box 79)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718520
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, 1998-2000 (Box 80)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718538
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, 2000-2001, undated (Box 81)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718546
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, undated (Box 82)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718553
  - Notebooks, Address Books, Date Books, undated (Box 83)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718561
- Series III: Correspondence, 6.25 Linear Feet 5 Paige Cartons